degreegrab.com 2010-11-21

# Degree Grab

**DegreeGrab.com** is owned and operated by Sardonic Enterprises, LLC 

Company Practices Regarding Your Privacy 

We at DegreeGrab.com and our affiliated companies worldwide are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites. DegreeGrab.com has established the following Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of DegreeGrab.com regarding information we collect on our network of web sites and through our other Internet advertising mediums, including but not limited to email, newsletters, and leave-behinds. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DegreeGrab.com does not own or control, or to people that DegreeGrab.com does not employ. 

**Information Collected by DegreeGrab.com**

Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information 

DegreeGrab.com collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the DegreeGrab.com site, the pages of the site you visited and the URL of the page you visited upon leaving the site. 

DegreeGrab.com may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information. 

**How Collected Information is Used**

The non-personally identifiable information that DegreeGrab.com collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. 

By the user submitting his/her personal and/or financial information on publisher’s site, the user is hereby granting written permission to publisher, its affiliated sites, sponsors, etc. for contact information. The user is also consenting to receive phone calls from publisher, its affiliates, and its partners for contact via telephone, and thereby, the user waives their right to file a claim with the FTC or any other agency in regards to these contacts or calls. 

**Our Privacy Policy and Outside Links**

This Privacy Policy only applies to this DegreeGrab.com Web site. Once you're outside of this DegreeGrab.com Web site, any information you submit is no longer in our control or governed by this privacy policy. You should be sure that you review the privacy policy of any site to which you link or redirect your browser and should not assume that any such Web site is operated by DegreeGrab.com or governed by this privacy policy. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out **

Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting DegreeGrab.com web sites. 

**Children's Privacy**

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), DegreeGrab.com is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

**Commitment**

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and DegreeGrab.com is constantly changing to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@DegreeGrab.com. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention. 

**Your Consent**

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to DegreeGrab.com processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy.
